Victor Matthews

 Penver, Colorado
 ■ victormmatthews@gmail.com
 □ (616) 970 0690
 in/victor-matthews-x
 ■ https://victormmatthews.me

SUMMARY

Experienced software engineer with a demonstrated history of working in supply chain management of the food & beverages industry and a focus on inventory control and material handling control systems. Skilled in Java, Angular, and SQL. Strong engineering professional, graduated from Ferris State University.

EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Engineer

Gordon Food Service | IT Warehouse Team

March 2016 - Present, Grand Rapids, MI

- · Working with the IT Warehouse team, I have helped develop and support the warehouse management system.
- · Subject matter expert on Inventory Control and Material Handling Control Systems.
- On a team of 14 people I played a big part in the most recent warehouse project where we created and deployed a new Angular app to replace old telnet devices in the warehouses.
- · Updated and revamped software used throughout the entire warehouse for receiving, selection, inventory control, and shipping.
- · Completed 22% of the 200+ bugs that came in over the 10 month roll-out of the software to all warehouses.

Asset Administrator

Gordon Food Service | North American Asset Management Team

May 2015 - March 2016, Grand Rapids, MI

- · Automated the internal IT hardware & software PO request system using JavaScript, resulting in faster throughput for PO requests.
- · Awarded the Gordon Food Service J&P Cup award, a yearly award given to one of the IT teams.
- · Implemented field validation for forms to make sure the user had all the information needed, based on their specific requests.
- · Added the ability for an Asset Administrator on the team to generate a PO number, save as a PDF, and store the request in the proper folder with a click of a button.

Sales Associate

Gordon Food Service

September 2013 - May 2015, Grand Rapids, MI

- · Working at a Gordon Food Service Retail Store in Grand Rapids, MI.
- \cdot I showed my work ethic and made connections that eventually got me a position in the corporate office as a Software Engineer more than a year before getting my degree.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science | Digital Media Software Engineering

Ferris State University · Grand Rapids, MI · 2017

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

5x Ferris State University College of Education & Human Services Dean's List of Scholars | 2014 - 2017

· Awarded honor roll due to high academic achievement

Gordon Food Service J&P Cup Winner | 2015 | North American Asset Management Team

 \cdot Awarded for work detailed in my role as an Asset Administrator with Gordon Food Service, automating and increasing throughput of PO Requests.

SKILLS

Back End: Java, SQL, C#

Front End: Angular 2+, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Misc: Git, Node.js, REST, Spring, Maven